girldressup.net 2012-06-06

# Play Free Dress Up Games at SevenGirlz.com

**1\. Privacy and information collection policy**

This privacy and information collection policy explain how we obtain information made available on the[ http://www.GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") website (the "Site"), and govern the information you provide us, whether actively (e.g., Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us) or passively (e.g., information we obtain through the use of Cookies). 

**2\. How We Obtain The Information We Make Available On The Site**

[GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") compiles information regarding websites from the publicly available "whois" databases which domain name registries and registrars publish on the Internet. We also obtain information regarding websites from other publicly available sources (e.g., Alexa). We then make that data available, along with a link to the websites, logos, thumbnail screenshots, in a centralized location at the Site. We also make available a map, which is nothing more than a spatial representation of otherwise publicly available information. 

**3\. What Information We Collect**

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") about you (i.e., users) from the Site unless you choose to provide it to us. This means that you can play games in [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games"), you do not need to inform us who you are or reveal any PII about yourself. 

However, when you register as a member at Registration in [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games"), we collect Personal Information including your email address, first name, last name, and birthday, or any information that is voluntarily provided by you. 

We maintain log files which contain Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. We do not link IP addresses to personal information. In general, we only use log files to monitor traffic on our Web sites and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of abuse, however, we may block certain IP addresses. 

**4\. How We Use It**

[GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") is committed to protecting your privacy. We will not sell your email address to any third party vendors. The information about age is mainly used to identify minors that need to get permission from their parents or legal guardian to become members at [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") (Minors in the US are defined as children under 13, in non-US minors are defined as under 16 of age.) 

We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the website [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games"). We do not send newsletters or mass emails. 

We have no control over third parties to whom you may give Personal Information through the use of [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games"). 

From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of additions or improvements to the [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") services as well as conduct member surveys in order to improve our service. 

We may also use personally identifiable user information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to users based on their demographic and behavioral information.  

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**5\. Cookie**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie enables us to collect information about your visits to [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games"). We may use this information to enhance your [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") experience and may share some information with our members, vendors, sponsors or others. 

You can turn off the cookie function in your web browser, then you won't be able to register as a member or log in. 

**6\. Parental Rights**

As a parent you have the right to review your minor child's personal information, have it deleted and refuse [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") to further collect information from your child. This would of course require a proper identification. Please contact us at Girldressup[at]Gmail.com   
(Minor in the US = under 13)   
(Minor in non-US= under 16) 

**7\. Contact**

If you have questions regarding the privacy statement or anything else, please contact us at Girldressup[at]Gmail.com 

This Terms of Use Agreement sets forth the standards of use of the [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") website - a non-violent and safe website for young children. Therefore, anyone who caught posting profanity, pornographic materials or links, or subject matter not fit for young children will be banned or deleted from this website. By using the www.[GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") website you ("user") agree to these terms and conditions. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this agreement, you should immediately cease all usage of this website. Girl Dress Up reserves the right to change the terms and conditions of this agreement without prior notice. 

**1\. Content & Suitability **

[GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") provides free access to dress-up games, girl games and related games. [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") will attempt to always provide a platform that is suitable for young children but you understand that since users of the service have the ability to post content (including images, games) that it may be possible for children to see inappropriate content before a member of staff has had the chance to remove it. 

[GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") requires users to the Website to be 13 years or older, if not they must be accompanied by a parent or guardian who is directly supervising them. If you are not 13 years of age, have your parents review these Terms of Use and help you register. 

**2 . Third-Party Sites**

Girl Dress Up includes links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. You acknowledge that Girl Dress Up is not responsible for the availability of, or the content located on or through, any third-party site.  

**3\. Limitation Of Liability**

It is [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games")'s policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") will immediately disable and remove games in question. 

**4\. Safety**

[GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") is committed to providing a safe and friendly environment for its users. We employ on a voluntary basis a number of staff which moderates the website and services. You should never give out any personal information to anyone and this includes your address, phone number, email, messenger or any other contact info. If you must do so you should seek your parents' advice first. We cannot be held responsible for what may happen should you decide to give out this information. 

**5\. Users' Responsibilities**

You ("User") may use the Website for lawful purposes only. You may not submit or transmit through the Website any material, or otherwise engage in any conduct that is unlawful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, libelous, deceptive, fraudulent, invasive of anothers privacy, tortuous, or contains explicit or graphic descriptions, or accounts of, sexual acts.  
You may not use the Website in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair our servers or networks, or interfere with any other partys use and enjoyment of the Website.  
No spam: You may not use the Website or any of our communication tools to transmit, directly or indirectly, any unsolicited bulk communications (including e-mails and instant messages). 

**6\. Users' Submissions**

Please note that any information, data, material or other communication you transmit or post to this Web Site will be deemed NOT to be confidential and non-proprietary ("Communications"). 

By sending [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") any information or material, you grant [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") the unrestricted, irrevocable, perpetual license to use, copy, have used, reproduce, display, modify, have modified, incorporate, sublicense, distribute or otherwise dispose of those information, data, material, and communication. 

You further agree that [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send us for any purposes for all commercial and non-commercial purposes. 

However, [GirlDressup.net](http://www.girldressup.net/ "Dress up Games") will not release your name or otherwise publish the fact that you submit materials or other information to us without your permission unless required to do so by law. 

Now that the legal stuff is out of the way, welcome to Girl Dress Up and thank you for visiting!
